Hello Hello Money Talk Welcome to my channel Money
Talk with Payal 100 Star Health Insurance
IPO's first day so we will
discuss about it that
what kind of response the company got
for this IPO today so come the page is open and will remain
open till 2 December if you are
interested in it then you should
apply on 2 December at least before 2 pm
so that you have a chance of getting it, it happens
after 2 pm sometimes
February prices come and you are not
able to apply its cut off price is ₹90 per
city but if you want to apply then
share it at these rupees but as the situation is visible today
it is still under subscribed
okay so if this third date itself
remains under subscribed then you can buy it for less than 98
because you will still have a
chance of getting it but if it gets
over subscribed by 2 December
then you will not have any points
apply for less than your hands phone so if you want you
can wait for third  To see
what kind of response it is getting, if it gets
subscribed inside, then you
can also apply through multiple lots, if you are really
interested in this IPO, and friend, you
can also apply below the Noida cutoff, which is the price band, here
your interest, you can easily apply on these lots,
if the share IPO
remains undersubscribed, then its one lot is of 16 six,
so when you apply
in multiple lots, you will be
allotted shares per lot if it is subscribed, and today a
very cold response has been received,
even the name of Rakesh Jhunjhunwala did not help in this,
Institutional investors Hero time
Non institutional investors 0.01 time
Retail investors 0.64 Science and
Improves, these shares are being allotted to them at a discount of Rs.80,
they have also
not shown interest,
Rohit, the camp of his own company, in 2010 three times today  I have
subscribed to it
but if we look at the first day then it does not
mean much, we cannot see it properly that on the
first day itself its response is lukewarm but it is
possible that tomorrow it will be fully
subscribed, this can happen
because on the first day
investors also see what to do,
they think about it and to save their interest, even the
girls, if they find
their face interesting, then to
save their interest they also
apply as much as possible on the third day, so
if you see that in the last few days the
maximum
number of applications are received
in the company's IPO, then today a very
lukewarm response is visible, okay, today this
data is the data till 5 pm,
in absolutely no category it is open,
subscription is also very lukewarm, this is what I got
from the phone, this is the news
second, if you want to see first whether I am
applying or not and if there is a question on it,
then I have an IPO review
playlist, there I have
I review every IPO and put it up, so I have made a Star Health
body and put it up for Tera Industries as well,
and you
can watch both these videos because both the IPOs of Taga
Industries are going to open tomorrow
and Star Health and Death have done so,
so both these are important videos for you,
so you will
go to my playlist in the tube of your review
and there you can see all these reviews,
I will also give the link in the comment
and secondly you can tell the bad news, its
grey market premium is equally bad,
from ₹13 to ₹15, right now its grey
market PM team is running, meaning and let's
insult the uncovered ₹15, let's say ₹15
paper ji MP is running on Rs.900 and this is also the
data till 5 o'clock only, okay, so 9 first,
friend, 15th, if we say, then this
is the highest till now because even people of ₹10 were
running on MP earlier, so according to the calculation, now we will
see ₹15 now  I wonder what happens,
but yes, the chances of getting a big listing gain are
very less. The way EPS is
visible, the market is quite cold.
Biscuit trading in the grey market is something special. So
basically, there is
not much erotic in it. But overall, if you should invest for the long term
or not,
for that you can see my Star Health IPO
review. In this, I have told you everything whether
you want to invest for the long term or for the short term. If
you want to invest for listing gains, then
you are investing in which Star,
please tell me by commenting.
If you need any more details about this, if you have any confusion, then please tell me by
commenting. I will cover whatever questions you have in the comments related to Star Health IPO, when
I will post it tomorrow, then
I will cover whatever questions you have in the comments related to Star Health IPO. Okay, so you must have liked this
video. If yes, then please
like, share and comment. If not, then
subscribe. We will meet again
with a new video. Thank you.